<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo Learn Documentation</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/uneurl/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hugo Learn Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fr-fr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/uneurl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown syntax</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/uneurl/cont/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/uneurl/cont/markdown/</guid>
      <description>This page is a shameful copy of the great Grav original page. Only difference is information about image customization (resizing, add CSS classes&amp;hellip;)
 Let&amp;rsquo;s face it: Writing content for the Web is tiresome. WYSIWYG editors help alleviate this task, but they generally result in horrible code, or worse yet, ugly web pages.
Markdown is a better way to write HTML, without all the complexities and ugliness that usually accompanies it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First child of the second child pafe</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/uneurl/cont/pages/second-child-page/truc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/uneurl/cont/pages/second-child-page/truc/</guid>
      <description>trrregergg</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shortcodes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/uneurl/cont/shortcodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/uneurl/cont/shortcodes/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses Markdown for its simple content format. However, there are a lot of things that Markdown doesn’t support well. You could use pure HTML to expand possibilities.
But this happens to be a bad idea. Everyone uses Markdown because it&amp;rsquo;s pure and simple to read even non-rendered. You should avoid HTML to keep it as simple as possible.
To avoid this limitations, Hugo created shortcodes. A shortcode is a simple snippet inside a page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/uneurl/basics/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/uneurl/basics/installation/</guid>
      <description>The following steps are here to help you initialize your new website. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know Hugo at all, we strongly suggest you to train by following this great documentation for beginners.
Create your project Hugo provides a new command to create a new website.
hugo new site &amp;lt;new_project&amp;gt;  Install the theme Install the Hugo-theme-learn theme by following this documentation
The theme&amp;rsquo;s repository is: https://github.com/matcornic/hugo-theme-learn.git
Basic configuration When building the website, you can set a theme by using --theme option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/uneurl/basics/configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/uneurl/basics/configuration/</guid>
      <description>Site configuration On top of Hugo global configuration, Hugo-theme-learn lets you define the following parameters :
[params] # Prefix URL to edit current page. Useful to give opportunity to people to create merge request for your doc. # See the config.toml file from this documentation site to have an example. editURL = &amp;quot;&amp;quot; # Author of the site, will be used in meta information author = &amp;quot;&amp;quot; # Description of the site, will be used in meta information description = &amp;quot;&amp;quot; # Shows a checkmark for visited pages on the menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archetypes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/uneurl/cont/archetypes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/uneurl/cont/archetypes/</guid>
      <description>Using the command: hugo new [relative new content path], you can start a content file with the date and title automatically set. While this is a welcome feature, active writers need more : archetypes.
It is pre-configured skeleton pages with default front matter. Please refer to the documentation for types of page to understand the differences.
Chapter To create a Chapter page, run the following commands
hugo new --kind chapter &amp;lt;name&amp;gt;/_index.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>