<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Content on Hugo Learn Theme</title>
    <link>https://matcornic.github.io/hugo-learn-doc/cont/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Content on Hugo Learn Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://matcornic.github.io/hugo-learn-doc/cont/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pages</title>
      <link>https://matcornic.github.io/hugo-learn-doc/cont/pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matcornic.github.io/hugo-learn-doc/cont/pages/</guid>
      <description>In Hugo, pages are the core of your site. Once it is configure, pages are definitely the added value to your documentation site.
Folders Organize your site like any other Hugo project. Typically, you will have a content folder with all your pages.
. └── content ├── brace | ├── yourselves.md &amp;lt;- http://example.com/brace/yourselves/ | ├── winter | | └── index.md &amp;lt;- http://example.com/brace/winter/ | └── index.md &amp;lt;- http://example.com/brace/ ├── is | ├── coming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown syntax</title>
      <link>https://matcornic.github.io/hugo-learn-doc/cont/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matcornic.github.io/hugo-learn-doc/cont/markdown/</guid>
      <description>This page is a shameful copy of the great Grav original page. Only difference is information about image customization (resizing, add CSS classes&amp;hellip;)
 Let&amp;rsquo;s face it: Writing content for the Web is tiresome. WYSIWYG editors help alleviate this task, but they generally result in horrible code, or worse yet, ugly web pages.
Markdown is a better way to write HTML, without all the complexities and ugliness that usually accompanies it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shortcodes</title>
      <link>https://matcornic.github.io/hugo-learn-doc/cont/shortcodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 16:50:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matcornic.github.io/hugo-learn-doc/cont/shortcodes/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses Markdown for its simple content format. However, there are a lot of things that Markdown doesn’t support well. You could use pure HTML to expand possibilities.
But this happens to be a bad idea. Everyone uses Markdown because it&amp;rsquo;s pure and simple to read even non-rendered. You should avoid HTML to keep it as simple as possible.
To avoid this limitations, Hugo created shortcodes. A shortcode is a simple snippet inside a page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archetypes</title>
      <link>https://matcornic.github.io/hugo-learn-doc/cont/archetypes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matcornic.github.io/hugo-learn-doc/cont/archetypes/</guid>
      <description>Using the command: hugo new [relative new content path], you can start a content file with the date and title automatically set. While this is a welcome feature, active writers need more : archetypes.
It is pre-configured skeleton pages with default front matter. Please refer to the documentation for types of page to understand the differences.
Chapter To create a Chapter page, run the following commands
hugo new --kind chapter &amp;lt;name&amp;gt;/_index.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>